Guide to the R. Stuart Hummel Family Papers M1607
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series IX. PHOTOGRAPHS, Circa 1870-2005
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Photo 9 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 22)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, duplicates, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, duplicates, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, duplicates, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel with China friends, photographs, miscellaneous materials, circa 1900-1927 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel with China friends, photographs, circa 1900-1927 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Photo 1 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 106, Folder 10, Item 25)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel with China friends, photographs, circa 1900-1927 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Photo 1 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 106, Folder 11, Item 12)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel with China friends, photographs, circa 1900-1927 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel with China friends, photographs, duplicates, circa 1900-1927 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel with China friends, photographs, negatives, circa 1900-1927 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College and Nanking and Shanghai, China, photograph album, circa 1900-1912 (Flat-box 107, Volume 1)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Egypt and Holy Land photo album, 1903 (Flat-box 108, Volume 1)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College and Nanking and Shanghai, China, photographs: duplicate copy prints of photos in box 107., circa 1900-1912 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College and Nanking and Shanghai, China, photographs: duplicate copy prints of photos in box 107., circa 1900-1912 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College and Nanking and Shanghai, China, photographs: duplicate copy prints of photos in box 107., circa 1900-1912 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College, photographs, miscellaneous materials, 1905-1908 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College, photographs, 1905-1908 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Photo 1 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 109, Folder 5, Item 10)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College, photographs, 1905-1908 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Photo 1 (Box 109, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 109, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 109, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 109, Folder 6, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 109, Folder 6, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 109, Folder 6, Item 6)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College, photographs, copy prints (unique), 1905-1908 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Simpson College, photographs, duplicates, 1905-1908 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, Methodist Girls School, Nanking, China, photographs, circa 1908 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Mildred and William F. Hummel, wedding photographs, 1912 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Photo 1 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 109, Folder 10, Item 14)
  - Mildred and William F. Hummel, wedding photographs, duplicates, 1912 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Mildred and William F. Hummel, wedding photographs, negatives, 1912 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - William F. Hummel photographs, circa 1890-1930 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Photo 1 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 109, Folder 13, Item 13)
  - William F. Hummel photographs, circa 1930-1970 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - William F. Hummel photographs, duplicates (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - William F. Hummel photographs, negatives (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - William F. Hummel, University of Chicago photographs, circa 1906-1908 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Photo 1 (Box 109, Folder 17, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 109, Folder 17, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 109, Folder 17, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 109, Folder 17, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 109, Folder 17, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 109, Folder 17, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 109, Folder 17, Item 7)
  - William F. Hummel, University of Chicago, Wehking family home, and China, photograph album, circa 1906-1915 (Flat-box 110, Volume 1)
  - William F. Hummel, University of Chicago, Wehking family home, and China, photo album, duplicates, circa 1906-1915 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - William F. Hummel, Warrenton, Missouri, photographs (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - William F. Hummel, China years, photographs, 1908-1927 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 111, Folder 3, Item 25)
  - William F. Hummel, China years, photographs, 1908-1927 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 25)
    - Photo 26 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 26)
    - Photo 27 (Box 111, Folder 4, Item 27)
  - William F. Hummel, China years, photographs, duplicates, 1908-1927 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - William F. Hummel, China years, photographs, negatives, 1908-1927 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Wehking, Lesseman, Krughoff, and Hummel families, photograph album; includes photos of Hummel family in China, circa 1906-1922 (Flat-box 277)
  - Kuling, China, photographs, circa 1907-1927 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 25)
    - Photo 26 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 26)
    - Photo 27 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 27)
    - Photo 28 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 28)
    - Photo 29 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 29)
    - Photo 30 (Box 111, Folder 7, Item 30)
  - Kuling, China, photographs, circa 1907-1927 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 25)
    - Photo 26 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 26)
    - Photo 27 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 27)
    - Photo 28 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 28)
    - Photo 29 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 29)
    - Photo 30 (Box 111, Folder 8, Item 30)
  - Kuling, China, photographs, circa 1907-1927 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 9, Item 23)
  - Kuling, China, photographs, duplicates, circa 1907-1927 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Kuling, China, photographs, negatives, circa 1907-1927 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Kuling, China, (photographs by David H. Grover), miscellaneous materials, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Kuling, China, (photographs by David H. Grover), copy prints (unique), 1922 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 13, Item 24)
  - Kuling, China, (photographs by David H. Grover), copy prints (unique), 1922 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 111, Folder 14, Item 25)
  - Kuling, China, (photographs by David H. Grover), negatives, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Shansi, China, photographs, circa 1918 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 16, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 16, Item 2)
  - Shansi, China, photographs, duplicates, circa 1918 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - China scenes and China friends, photographs, miscellaneous materials, circa 1907-1912 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - China scenes and China friends, photographs, circa 1907-1912 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 25)
    - Photo 26 (Box 111, Folder 19, Item 26)
  - China scenes and China friends, photographs, circa 1907-1912 (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 111, Folder 20, Item 25)
  - China scenes and China friends, photographs, circa 1907-1912 (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 21, Item 21)
  - China scenes and China friends, photographs, circa 1907-1912 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 22, Item 24)
  - China scenes and China friends, photographs, copy prints (unique), circa 1907-1912 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 23, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 23, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 23, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 23, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 23, Item 5)
  - China scenes and China friends, photographs, negatives, circa 1907-1912 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - China scenes and China friends, postcards, circa 1907-1912 (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Photo 1 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 25)
    - Photo 26 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 26)
    - Photo 27 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 27)
    - Photo 28 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 28)
    - Photo 29 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 29)
    - Photo 30 (Box 111, Folder 25, Item 30)
  - Muriel Boone, Nanking, China, photograph album, circa 1917 (Flat-box 112, Volume 1)